maxmailhq.com 2019-03-22

# Privacy Policy | Maxmail

This policy sets out the way that CyberCom collects and uses information collected on this website.

 **Information Collection and Use**

Cybercom Hospitality Solutions Limited (CyberCom) is the sole owner of the information collected on this site www.maxmailhq.com (Website) We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. CyberCom collects information from our users at several different points on the Website.

 **Registration**

In order to use the Website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on the Website for which they have expressed interest.

 **Account Activation**

We request information from the user on our account activation and credit purchase. Here a user must provide financial information (credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing and credit reference purposes for filling customers' orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to (contact) the user.

 **  
Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information  
**If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may deactivate it by making the change on our member information page [or by emailing our Customer Support <https://www.maxmailhq.com/support> or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

 **Newsletters & Communication from CyberCom **

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe, simply click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email to opt-out of our newsletters

 **Service Related Information**

We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account, write to us at <https://www.maxmailhq.com/support> or call +64 9 368 5017 to close your account.

 **Collecting other information on Website’s visitors**

CyberCom _collects_ non-Personal Information on Website visits by users including, without limitation, which sections of the Website are most frequently visited, how often, and for how long. This data is always used as aggregated, non-Personal Information, and may be shared with CyberCom’s partners to provide them with information relating to how visitors 'use' the Website. This is done for the purpose of providing you with the best and most efficient career management and recruitment services. The information we automatically collect may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, software configuration, aggregate use information, geographical location data, operating system and use of Cookies. If you do not have a Maxmail Account, we will not usually be able to identify you from this information.

 **IP Addresses**

Website's web servers gather your IP address to assist with the diagnosis of problems or support issues with our services, and to monitor the use of our Website, including the monitoring of the location of our users.

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Website. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Website, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on the Website. The Website will log people out of a secure session after 2 hours of inactivity by a user.

 **Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Website, track user's movement(s), and gather broad geolocation information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information neither for the purposes of New Zealand law nor for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679 nor for the purposes of any other jurisdiction.

 **Third Party Measurement**

In order to better understand our users, CyberCom utilises third party measurement companies to assess Website and mobile Website traffic. A tracking code is used to collect the following information on the usage of the Website:

  * The number of page views (or page impressions) that occur on the Website;
  * The number of unique visitors to the Website;
  * How long these unique visitors (on average) spend on the Website when they do visit; and
  * Common entry and exit points into the Website.

This aggregated, non-Personal Information is collated and provided to CyberCom to assist in analysing the usage of the Website. This data is also accessible by media organisations and research companies, for the purpose of conducting industry comparisons with other Internet websites.

 **How we collect personal data**

If you sign up for a Maxmail account and/or services, we will collect basic information about you including your name, email address and telephone number. You may provide this information to us directly, or by signing in to your account/service with a third party, including without limitation, Google (see “Third Party Data Collection” below). We will use the information that we collect about you to:

  * create and maintain your account;
  * allow you to log in to Maxmail;
  * contact you about your account and/or the services that CyberCom offers (see “Maxmail Updates” below).

 **Sharing of Non Personal Information**

We may share aggregated geolocation information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.  

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for services. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

 **Sharing of Personal Information**

We will disclose the personal information we hold about you to:

  1. our group companies and affiliates;
  2. CyberCom’s service providers, including IT hosting companies;
  3. payment service providers;
  4. third party companies in the event that Cybercom is involved in a corporate transaction such as an actual or potential merger, joint venture, consolidation or asset sale;
  5. professional advisors such as attorneys, accountants, auditors, financial and other professionals;
  6. regulatory authorities including tax authorities; and
  7. law enforcement agencies, courts and other relevant tribunals.

We will use the information you provide in your Profile to:

  * contact you on matters related to your account, including without limitation, to request any additional information and/or documentation;
  * tailor the products and services offered through the Website to you, including without limitation, to perform any suitability or appropriateness assessments for using our services and/or products, such as our high-leveraged trading services and Social Trading Features;
  * maintain administrative records relating to our business;
  * set up security measures to secure your account, including without limitation, carry out two-factor authentication; and
  * provide you with notices related to your account, general updates, market updates and other marketing materials, including without limitation, the services and products offered by CyberCom .

We process your personal information using data centers located located outside the European Union, including in New Zealand (where laws have been recognised as providing the same level of data protection as in the European Union). If you would like further information about the safeguards in place for transfers of personal information to our group companies or other third parties outside of the European Union, under the applicable data protection laws, please contact us (see _https://www.maxmailhq.com/contact-us_ ).

 **Third Party Data Collection**

When you use or connect to Website by or through a Third Party Platform, such as Facebook or another Website, you allow us to access and/or collect certain information from your Third Party Platform profile/account (or via any cookies placed on your device by such Third Party Platform), as permitted by the terms of the agreement and your privacy settings with the Third Party Platform. We will share such information with the Third Party Platform for their use.

We will share some of the information we collect from you on install of the mobile app with vendors and other service providers who are engaged by, or working with, us in connection with the operation of the services we provide to you. This may also be shared with these parties for analytics purposes, which may require the reproduction and display of your information in an aggregated and anonymized manner that will not in any way identify you.

 **Automated analysis of your personal information**

We may use the personal information you provide to us, or that we gather when you use the Website to tailor Maxmail to your Profile. CyberCom will carry out this analysis automatically, and in most cases without human intervention. You can update the information in your Profile at any time by visiting the “Account” page in the Settings menu. We recommend that you update your Profile regularly, to ensure that the Maxmail functions offered to you are appropriate for your circumstances. If you have any questions about the automated analysis of your personal information, please contact us (see https://www.maxmailhq.com/contact-us).

**Our legal basis for using your personal information**

  1. Entering into and performing the contract with you: If you have an Maxmail account or have registered to the Website or service, our legal basis for processing your personal information is that it is necessary for the performance of CyberCom ’s terms and conditions, terms of business and/or terms of use, as the case may be, and to provide a service to you. With respect to a Maxmail account, this includes facilitating access to our platform, processing payments and executing trades.
  2. For other justifiable grounds, including legal obligation and legitimate interests: We process your personal information where necessary for CyberCom to comply with legal and regulatory obligations we are under, and also where it is necessary for legitimate interests we have in conducting our business. These include without limitation:

  * Learning about your interests and preferences to contact you with information that is relevant to you and helping us target marketing communications and adverts so that they are more relevant to you.
  * Analysing and continually improving the Website and our services and helping us pilot test versions of the Website internally to develop new features and ensure the efficient running of CyberCom’s services.
  * Detecting and reducing fraud and credit risk.

 **  
Customer Testimonials/Reviews/Comments**

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on the Website which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

 **Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at <https://www.maxmailhq.com/support>. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

 **Security**

We protect your personal information by using data security technology and using tools such as firewalls and data encryption. We also require that you use a personal username and password every time you access your account online. As set out in the relevant Maxmail’s terms and conditions, terms of business and/or terms of use, as the case may be, you must not share your password with anyone else. We restrict access to personal information at our offices so that only officers and/or employees with a genuine need can access it. CyberCom takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Website, your information is protected both online and off-line.  
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with industry-standard strong encryption - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked door.  
Users of the Maxmail Service must realize that although CyberCom employs high levels of security, no data transmission over the internet can be 100% safe.

Therefore, use of CyberCom's Messaging is at the client's own risk.

Furthermore, users must be aware that sending messages with CyberCom will have a similar level of security and reliability as that of Mobile Phone Networks.

CyberCom, its employees and contractors will not be held liable for any loss or damage whatsoever, incurred through the use of CyberCom SMS Messaging, including loss of information due to carrier failure, network failure or negligence on the part of CyberCom , its employees or contractors.

Please refer to our Terms and Conditions and Disclaimer for more information.

 **Maxmail Updates**

If you sign up for a Maxmail account, Website and/or service, we may use your personal information to send you inapp push notifications, SMS or email communications. These communications may relate to your trading activity, account status, social interactions on Maxmail, or may include Cybercom’s updates and promotions. You can opt out of receiving updates at any time by clicking the “ _Unsubscribe_ ” link at the bottom of any email from Maxmail, or by visiting https://www.maxmailhq.com/support.

 **  
Retention of personal information**

The period for which we will retain personal information will vary depending on the purposes that it was collected for, as well as the requirements of any applicable law or regulation. If you have an account with Maxmail, we will store your personal information for as long as you maintain that account, and after you cease holding an account, for as long as we are required to by laws and regulations that are applicable to us.

 **  
Minors**

Maxmail is not available for users under the age of 18 (or the age of legal consent for the jurisdiction the user is located in) (a “ **minor** ”). We do not knowingly collect personal information from or about minors. If you are a minor, you should not download or use any of our services nor provide any personal information to us. If we become aware that a minor has shared any information with us, we will delete such information. If you have any reason to believe that a minor has shared any information with us, please contact us at <https://www.maxmailhq.com/support>.

 **  
Links**

The Website may include links to other websites on the internet. We are not responsible for the content of these websites or for any other privacy practices on these internet websites. You should read the terms of use and the privacy statements of any such websites. Our terms of use and our privacy policy apply only to information collected by us in accordance with this Policy

 **  
When you Contact Us**

If you contact us by telephone, email, post or using another function offered by Maxmail, e.g. chat, we will collect any information that you choose to give Us. We will use this information to review, investigate and respond to any comment or question that you may raise. Please note that we record all telephone calls made to us.

 **Your rights**

Individuals whose information we hold may be entitled to access their personal information, or to request that it is erased, that its processing is restricted, or that any inaccurate personal information is rectified. You may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information, or in some circumstances to obtain a copy of the personal information in machine readable format. Any such request should be submitted in writing to: <https://www.maxmailhq.com/support>

## More Information About Privacy

For more information about privacy issues in New Zealand and protecting your privacy, visit the (https://www.privacy.org.nz).

 **Jurisdictional Information**

 **European Union**

CyberCom does not collect information which is deemed to be information falling within special categories of personal data for the purposes of Art. 9 of the GDPR through this Website. ThereforeArt. 27 of the GDPR does not apply.

 **Jurisdiction and Applicable Law**

Collecting, retaining and sharing of the information by or in connection with this Website is governed by New Zealand privacy laws.

 **Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. You are responsible for keeping yourself up to date with any such changes to this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
